<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/20/wsj_2018@2018@wsj@nw@en@on">
As vice president / national - government relations , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Womack</ENAMEX> will work with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">P-AMP-G</ENAMEX> 's top management and with the company 's government - relations staff `` to represent <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">P-AMP-G</ENAMEX> 's interests at the federal level , '' said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">John G. Smale</ENAMEX> , chairman and chief executive officer .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Smale</ENAMEX> said the appointment `` recognizes the growing influence of government on our business . ''
</DOC>
