<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/20/wsj_2085@2085@wsj@nw@en@on">
He succeeds <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">John A. Boudreau</ENAMEX> , who resigned for personal reasons .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Tanner</ENAMEX> had been president of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Penn Pacific 's</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">National Southwest Capital Group</ENAMEX> subsidiary .
He has also agreed to become president of a new subsidiary to be formed to make future acquisitions , the company said .
</DOC>
