<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/20/wsj_2076@2076@wsj@nw@en@on">
NEWSPAPERS :
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Media General</ENAMEX> said it has had inquiries from potential buyers and expects to complete a sale in <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">1989</ENAMEX> .
It would n't discuss a price .
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Lee Dirks -AMP- Associates</ENAMEX> is to sell the chains .
</DOC>
