<DOC DOCNO="bn/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0014@0014@p2.5_a2e@bn@en@on">
On his side , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Nabil Abu Rudeina</ENAMEX> , Consultant to the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Palestinian</ENAMEX> Presidency , said the task at this stage is the demand for serious negotiations to implement the Road Map and the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Arab</ENAMEX> Peace Initiative which is based on the <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">fourth of June</ENAMEX> borders of land for peace and foremost <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Jerusalem</ENAMEX> .
Ah what is important to us is to see serious negotiations on the negotiation table on the basis of the <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">fourth of June</ENAMEX> ah land for peace and , foremost <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Jerusalem</ENAMEX> .
Ah regarding the issue of refugees ah it is -- ah what came in the Road Map and in the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Arab</ENAMEX> Peace Initiative is a fair and agreed upon solution , according to resolution <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one hundred ninety - four</ENAMEX> .
This is the official <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Palestinian</ENAMEX> position , and this is what we committed to , the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Arab</ENAMEX> legitimacy and the international legitimacy .
If the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Palestinians</ENAMEX> form a new government that commits to implementing the Road Map and release <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Gilad Shalit</ENAMEX> , I will offer <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Abbas</ENAMEX> an immediate meeting in order to have a real and open dialogue .
I realize the importance of releasing <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Palestinian</ENAMEX> detainees .
I promise that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the Israeli government</ENAMEX> will be willing to release many <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Palestinians</ENAMEX> in return for <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Shalit</ENAMEX> returning home safe to his family .
</DOC>
