<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/14/wsj_1472@1472@wsj@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Moody 's Investors Service Inc.</ENAMEX> said it lowered the ratings of some <ENAMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 145 million</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Pinnacle</ENAMEX> debt because of `` accelerating deficiency in liquidity , '' which it said was evidenced by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Pinnacle</ENAMEX> 's elimination of dividend payments .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Henry Sargent Jr.</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Pinnacle</ENAMEX> executive vice president , said the action `` wo n't really have any effect on us .
The rating agency said it lowered the ratings on <ENAMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 75 million</ENAMEX> of the holding company 's convertible subordinated Eurodebentures to B - 3 from B - 1 .
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">MeraBank</ENAMEX> 's rating for short - term deposits remains Not Prime .
Securities of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">MeraBank</ENAMEX> were placed under review <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">last May</ENAMEX> , and will remain under review for downgrade , the agency said .
</DOC>
