<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/15/wsj_1579@1579@wsj@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Avondale Industries Inc.</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">New Orleans</ENAMEX> , received a <ENAMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 23 million</ENAMEX> contract from the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Navy</ENAMEX> to enlarge by <ENAMEX TYPE="PERCENT">50 %</ENAMEX> the capacity of an auxiliary oiler .
The award results from the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Navy</ENAMEX> 's exercising of an option in an earlier contract it awarded <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Avondale</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
