<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/11/wsj_1116@1116@wsj@nw@en@on">
Your <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">Oct. 2</ENAMEX> editorial `` <ENAMEX TYPE="WORK_OF_ART">Reding , Wrighting -AMP- Erithmatic</ENAMEX> '' on the recent `` education summit '' was like most pieces on the subject of education : It had little to say .
Unfortunately , the comment was buried in another article , so it could not stand out in an education context .
In the Manager 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Journal</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Atsushi Kageyama</ENAMEX> , in commenting on many differences between <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">American</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Japanese</ENAMEX> culture , said , `` <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Japanese</ENAMEX> children are raised in a way many <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Americans</ENAMEX> would find severe .
Unless parents and educators alike start to develop more discipline in children , all the worthy concern , discussions and actions will not solve the problem .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Allen B. Richards</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Peterborough</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">N.H</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
