<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/09/wsj_0955@0955@wsj@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Richard Breeden</ENAMEX> had n't noticed that his new desk had just <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">four</ENAMEX> telephone lines and <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one</ENAMEX> phone .
It was , after all , <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">only his second full day</ENAMEX> as chairman of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the Securities and Exchange Commission</ENAMEX> .
With other anxious calls pouring in , he recalls , `` I 'd either have to disconnect <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the New York Stock Exchange</ENAMEX> or go out to the secretary 's desk . ''
It wo n't happen again .
But unlike Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ruder</ENAMEX> , who during the <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">1987</ENAMEX> crash damaged himself by saying rather offhandedly that the markets might be closed , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> is turning the market drop to his own advantage , using it to further his agenda for the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">SEC</ENAMEX> .
In an interview and in congressional testimony , he repeatedly points to the recent <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">190</ENAMEX> - point plunge in the Dow Jones Industrial Average -- the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORDINAL">second</ENAMEX> - largest ever -- as evidence of the need for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Congress</ENAMEX> to give the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">SEC</ENAMEX> the ability to better monitor leveraged buy - out loan activity by brokerage firms and to track big trades in the market .
He believes the tax code encourages the use of debt instead of stock and may fuel leveraged buy - outs , an area the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">SEC</ENAMEX> does n't regulate directly but one where it wields influence both on Wall Street and in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Congress</ENAMEX> .
Also unlike Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ruder</ENAMEX> , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> appears to be in a position to get somewhere with his agenda .
As a former <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">White House</ENAMEX> aide who worked closely with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Congress</ENAMEX> , he is savvy in the ways of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Washington</ENAMEX> .
But Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">39 - year - old</ENAMEX> securities lawyer , has skirted some of the heftier issues facing the financial markets .
He may be waiting to see the results of several pending <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">SEC</ENAMEX> studies of junk market liquidity and disclosure rules .
He also has kept a close wrap on the names of people under consideration for the crucial post of enforcement director at the commission , a job vacant since <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">the summer</ENAMEX> .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> 's selection will be scrutinized as an important signal about the strength of his commitment to continuing the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">SEC</ENAMEX> 's high - profile pursuit of insider trading and market manipulation on Wall Street .
Members of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the Senate Banking Committee</ENAMEX> know Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> from working on the thrift - bailout bill , and the relationship generally remains warm .
As a regulator charged with restoring investor confidence , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> avoided making market - jarring comments and worked to gather information critical to Wall Street and to other government agencies .
Not everyone has jumped on the <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> bandwagon , however .
Some in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Washington</ENAMEX> contend that it 's too soon to tell whether Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> will help or hinder the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">SEC</ENAMEX> .
`` I do n't think this was a real test , '' says <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one</ENAMEX> congressional aide .
For some at the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">SEC</ENAMEX> , an agency that covets its independence , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> may be too much of a <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Washington</ENAMEX> insider .
They worry that Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> also will roll over when told to do so by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the White House</ENAMEX> .
Stunned , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> turned to his market - monitoring computer , which by then was next to his desk .
It showed the DJIA up <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">30</ENAMEX> points .
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">SEC</ENAMEX> staffers soon determined that a widely watched stock - market service , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Quotron</ENAMEX> , had miscalculated the industrial average .
`` It was the plunge that did n't happen , '' he says .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> also is trying to use a far more catastrophic event -- the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">California</ENAMEX> earthquake -- to move another rule change past <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Congress</ENAMEX> .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Breeden</ENAMEX> , not missing a chance to press his agenda , cited the earthquake .
</DOC>
