<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/19/wsj_1929@1929@wsj@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Egon Krenz</ENAMEX> , the man tapped <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">yesterday</ENAMEX> to become <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">East Germany 's</ENAMEX> new leader , faces the same task that has fallen to neighboring socialist colleagues : reforming a country in crisis .
But unlike the other new leaders in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">the East Bloc</ENAMEX> , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Krenz</ENAMEX> will face an immediate threat to his nation 's very existence : <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">German</ENAMEX> reunification .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Krenz</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">age 52</ENAMEX> , is known as an old - guard ironfist , one likely to continue the method of running a country that <ENAMEX TYPE="FAC">the Berlin Wall</ENAMEX> made famous .
Even if he were to change his stripes and become <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">another Milton Friedman</ENAMEX> , however , he would still stand a good chance of losing a country .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Krenz</ENAMEX> almost certainly will be a younger version of <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Erich Honecker</ENAMEX> , his rigid predecessor as dictator .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Krenz</ENAMEX> has followed much the same career path as Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Honecker</ENAMEX> : Both spent <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">years</ENAMEX> overseeing <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the Freie Deutsche Jugend</ENAMEX> , the youth group that is the communist regime 's principal tool for stamping young <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Germans</ENAMEX> into socialist citizens .
Faced with another Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Honecker</ENAMEX> , so many despairing <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">East Germans</ENAMEX> are likely to flee that the <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">two</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">German</ENAMEX> peoples will get their reunification , de facto , on <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">West German</ENAMEX> ground .
But if <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">East Germany 's</ENAMEX> arthritic <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Politburo</ENAMEX> does loosen up enough to permit Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Krenz</ENAMEX> to make serious efforts at reform , he will face a challenge just as fundamental .
Abandoning socialism means abandoning the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">East German</ENAMEX> state 's reason for existence , and with it the justification for its watchdogs and its <ENAMEX TYPE="FAC">Wall</ENAMEX> .
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Krenz</ENAMEX> may need a bit of time to consolidate his empire , which would do a lot to promote Reunification Scenario One .
Cartoonists in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">West Germany</ENAMEX> have already mocked the exodus by imagining an advertisement placed by Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Honecker</ENAMEX> : `` Wanted : <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one</ENAMEX> people . ''
The <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">West German</ENAMEX> embassies in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Prague</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Budapest</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Warsaw</ENAMEX> are continuing to find refugees at their gates .
But with world - wide opinion -- even , apparently in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Moscow</ENAMEX> -- against <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">East Germany</ENAMEX> , the country would have to turn itself into an <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Albania</ENAMEX> to clamp down further on refugees .
There have been some reports that Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Krenz</ENAMEX> is moving to `` soften '' his reputation , notably rumors that it was he who kept <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">East Germany 's</ENAMEX> state police off protesters ' backs at the country 's dismal <ENAMEX TYPE="ORDINAL">40th</ENAMEX> anniversary celebrations <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">earlier this month</ENAMEX> .
But even if he effects a <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Hyde</ENAMEX> - to - Jekyll transformation , he will face a serious ideological crisis and Reunification Scenario Two .
When <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Poland</ENAMEX> moves to reform , it can at least lean on its past : However flawed and short - lived <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Joseph Pilsudski 's</ENAMEX> interwar republic , it was a nonsocialist democracy .
Beyond that , it has to compete with <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">West Germany</ENAMEX> for a claim to the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">German</ENAMEX> identity .
Up to now , the main weapon of the `` worker and peasant state '' has been the ideology of socialism .
With talk <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">today</ENAMEX> of a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORDINAL">second</ENAMEX> economic miracle in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">West Germany</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">East Germany</ENAMEX> no longer can content itself with being the economic star in a loser league .
Without <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Moscow</ENAMEX> 's military and party behind it , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">East Germany</ENAMEX> runs the risk of disintegrating .
If it goes capitalist , and increases trade with <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">West Germany</ENAMEX> , it will convert itself , willy - nilly , into an economic annex of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the Federal Republic</ENAMEX> .
There may be forces that would delay this scenario .
Ideologues are the last to surrender , and <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Germans</ENAMEX> are an ideological people .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Helmut Kohl 's</ENAMEX> governing conservative coalition is proving admirably true to the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">West German</ENAMEX> constitution by making <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">more than 500,000</ENAMEX> people of <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">German</ENAMEX> descent automatic citizens <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">this year</ENAMEX> alone .
`` The main problem , '' Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Reinhold</ENAMEX> said in an <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">East German</ENAMEX> radio interview monitored by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Radio Free Europe</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Munich</ENAMEX> , stems from the fact that `` the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">GDR</ENAMEX> is different '' from other <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">East European</ENAMEX> states .
`` What kind of right to exist , '' he asked , `` would a capitalist <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">German Democratic Republic</ENAMEX> have alongside a capitalist <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Federal Republic</ENAMEX> ? ''
That 's a question <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">East Germany</ENAMEX> ca n't answer easily , no matter what its new leader does .
</DOC>
