<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/19/wsj_1959@1959@wsj@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">AVX Corp.</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Unitrode Corp.</ENAMEX> said they completed the previously reported sale of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Unitrode</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">San Diego</ENAMEX> - based <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Passive Components</ENAMEX> division to <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">AVX</ENAMEX> .
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Passive Components</ENAMEX> makes capacitors and filters used to protect electronics .
</DOC>
