<DOC DOCNO="bn/p2.5_c2e/00/p2.5_c2e_0004@0004@p2.5_c2e@bn@en@on">
It 's <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">close to year end</ENAMEX> , and car manufacturers and dealers have <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one</ENAMEX> by <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one</ENAMEX> fired off their last round of price wars for <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">this year</ENAMEX> .
Compared to the situation of price reductions in <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">previous years</ENAMEX> , it is neither the relatively price - sensitive economic car models nor the slow - selling cars that are leading the wave of price cuts at <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">this year - end</ENAMEX> ; rather the medium - grade cars have become the main force of this <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">year</ENAMEX> 's price reductions .
Considering the prices , uh , people feel that a discount of over <ENAMEX TYPE="QUANTITY">20,000 Yuan</ENAMEX> in this period is quite appropriate .
Among these , the reduction rate is larger for smaller and mid-sized cars , such as <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Honda</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">City</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Toyota</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">Vios</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Hyundai</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">Accent</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Chevy</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">Lova</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Honda</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">Fit</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Hyundai</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">Elantra</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Hyundai</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">Sonata</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Toyota</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">Crown</ENAMEX> , and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Honda</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT">Accord</ENAMEX> , where price reductions ranged from about <ENAMEX TYPE="PERCENT">10 percent</ENAMEX> to <ENAMEX TYPE="PERCENT">20 percent</ENAMEX> .
This is also the main reason why car prices have all dropped at <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">the end of the year</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
