<DOC DOCNO="nw/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0013@0013@p2.5_a2e@nw@en@on">
Rome , 12 - 2 -LRB- AFP -RRB- - Title holder <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Inter Milan</ENAMEX> continued its advance and positive results and achieved its <ENAMEX TYPE="ORDINAL">11th</ENAMEX> win against its guest <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Siena</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="QUANTITY">2</ENAMEX> - <ENAMEX TYPE="QUANTITY">0</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">today , Saturday</ENAMEX> , in the opening of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORDINAL">14th</ENAMEX> round of the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Italian</ENAMEX> soccer series .
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Inter Milan</ENAMEX> has not suffered a single defeat in the local championship since the beginning of the season -LRB- <ENAMEX TYPE="QUANTITY">11</ENAMEX> wins and <ENAMEX TYPE="QUANTITY">3</ENAMEX> ties -RRB- after it was given the title following its revocation from <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Juventus</ENAMEX> , which dropped to <ENAMEX TYPE="ORDINAL">second</ENAMEX> place when a number of points were transferred from its total to its neighbor <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Milan</ENAMEX> , the runner - up , because of their involvement in the score - tampering scandal .
Later , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Roma 2</ENAMEX> plays with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Atalanta Bergamo</ENAMEX> and the round concludes <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">tomorrow Sunday</ENAMEX> with <ENAMEX TYPE="QUANTITY">8</ENAMEX> matches .
</DOC>
