<DOC DOCNO="nw/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0038@0038@p2.5_a2e@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">The Board of Muslim Scholars</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> denounced <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Al - Maliki</ENAMEX> government 's request to the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">American</ENAMEX> occupation forces to prolong their stay in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> .
The statement added that this is an expected step from a government under an oppressive occupation claiming that its presence is necessary to spread security and stability in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> and for <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> to transition to the realm of freedom , democracy and prosperity , of which we continue to hear but see no traces or existence in our land .
This is the fact of the situation in general in our country , particularly the security situation , which has declined throughout the lean years of the occupation to such bad , deteriorating conditions that it can not be hidden from anyone , near or far , so much so that the harbingers of disaster and strife are looming .
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">The Board</ENAMEX> went on in its statement that such a step confirms what we have always said : that the political process under occupation will not succeed in bringing sovereignty back to <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> , because the occupation will remain in control of it .
Neither the government nor the parliament will have an effective will against the will of the occupier , and the members of the government stubbornly refuse to admit this fact , whereas events prove it day after day .
</DOC>
