<DOC DOCNO="nw/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0024@0024@p2.5_a2e@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Lahoud</ENAMEX> asserted that any intervention by <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">the United States of America</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">French</ENAMEX> President <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Jacques Chirac</ENAMEX> is likely to impede all efforts being exerted to end the abnormal situation which <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Lebanon</ENAMEX> is currently experiencing .
He reaffirmed that the first task of the new government is to reach a decision on the issue of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the International Tribunal</ENAMEX> , enact a new law for legislative elections , and hold the elections as soon as possible so that the parliament can elect the next president of the republic by the deadline stipulated in the constitution .
For his part , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ismail</ENAMEX> said that he transmitted a verbal message from President <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Al - Bashir</ENAMEX> to <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Lahoud</ENAMEX> in which he expressed his " concern about the developments , and the importance for all institutions and active forces to hold back this escalation and transfer the dialogue to meeting halls under the dome of the parliament , and reach an expanded government that includes the political forces , " noting that there is concern by all <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Lebanese</ENAMEX> parties that things could get worse and that there is consensus about the preference for moving the dialogue from the streets to the parliament , the importance of expanding the government , and that the opposition forces should effectively participate in it .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ismail</ENAMEX> also visited with Prime Minister <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Fouad Siniora</ENAMEX> in the governmental palace and reiterated his previous positions .
</DOC>
