<DOC DOCNO="nw/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0027@0027@p2.5_a2e@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Turkish</ENAMEX> police announced yesterday that a terrorist group consisting of <ENAMEX TYPE="QUANTITY">10</ENAMEX> people has been disbanded .
The group included a lawyer who claimed in an interview with an <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Islamic</ENAMEX> magazine <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">a year ago</ENAMEX> that he was the head of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Al - Qaeda</ENAMEX> organization in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Turkey</ENAMEX> .
A security source said the police had kept the lawyer , whose name they did not disclose , under surveillance after he gave the press interview and located the remaining members of the network who contacted the lawyer through his email on the internet .
The police arrested <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Syrian</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Loay Saqa</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Diyarbakir</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">August 2005</ENAMEX> on suspicion of being the assistant of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Al - Qaeda 's</ENAMEX> former leader in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Abu Musab Al - Zarqawi</ENAMEX> , and <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Tunisian</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Malik Sharahil</ENAMEX> , both accused of plotting to blow up an <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Israeli</ENAMEX> tourist ship near the port of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Antalya</ENAMEX> , also on the <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Mediterranean</ENAMEX> .
The security source said that a computer CD had been found in the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Turkish</ENAMEX> lawyer 's house which laboratory tests revealed contained materials that would explode in the event of it being played , and this is the first time <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Turkish</ENAMEX> security forces have come across such explosives .
</DOC>
