<DOC DOCNO="nw/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0008@0008@p2.5_a2e@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mitsutaka Uchikoshi</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">35 year</ENAMEX> old <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Japanese</ENAMEX> man , went missing on <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">the seventh of last October</ENAMEX> , according to news agencies and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the British Broadcasting Company</ENAMEX> " B. B. C. , " after his attempt to descend <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Mount Rokko</ENAMEX> in western <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Japan</ENAMEX> .
The medical team that found <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Uchikoshi</ENAMEX> said , according to the agency " U. B. A. , " that they were stunned when they discovered he was still alive .
" I fell down in a green area , and at <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">first</ENAMEX> I felt the warmth of the sun .
" At <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">first</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Uchikoshi</ENAMEX> 's temperature dropped below the normal level , a state similar to hibernation , " said Dr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Shinichi Sato</ENAMEX> , adding that " His brain was protected and did not suffer any damage and is now <ENAMEX TYPE="PERCENT">100 %</ENAMEX> recovered . "
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Uchikoshi</ENAMEX> was released from the hospital and returned home <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">last Tuesday</ENAMEX> after it was confirmed he had fully recovered .
</DOC>
