<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/05/wsj_0510@0510@wsj@nw@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Doskocil Cos.</ENAMEX> said its bank - debt payments have been extended until <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">May 31 , 1990</ENAMEX> , to give it more time to sell its <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Wilson Foods Corp.</ENAMEX> retail and fresh meat operations .
The company was to repay <ENAMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 58 million</ENAMEX> in debt on <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">Dec. 31</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 15 million</ENAMEX> on <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">March 31</ENAMEX> .
The company acquired the debt when it paid <ENAMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 155 million</ENAMEX> to purchase <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Wilson</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">last year</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
