<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/02/wsj_0268@0268@wsj@nw@en@on">
Many thanks for <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Alexander Cockburn 's</ENAMEX> comic masterpiece -LRB- `` <ENAMEX TYPE="WORK_OF_ART">U.S. . Economy : A House Built on Junk - Bond Sand</ENAMEX> , '' <ENAMEX TYPE="WORK_OF_ART">Viewpoint</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">Oct. 19</ENAMEX> -RRB- .
I await his sequel : the economic and social resiliency of the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">San Francisco Bay</ENAMEX> area and the outstanding work of the local governments and the private charitable organizations there as metaphors for the supremacy of whatever failed system Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Cockburn</ENAMEX> now believes in .
It should be a scream .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">William S. Smith</ENAMEX>
</DOC>
