<DOC DOCNO="nw/wsj/13/wsj_1327@1327@wsj@nw@en@on">
At <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">age eight</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Josephine Baker</ENAMEX> was sent by her mother to a white woman 's house to do chores in exchange for meals and a place to sleep -- a place in the basement with the coal .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bricktop</ENAMEX> , another <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">American</ENAMEX> black woman who found a measure of fame in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Paris</ENAMEX> , said : `` I do n't think I 've ever known anyone with a less complicated view of life , or whose life was more complicated than <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Josephine</ENAMEX> 's . ''
Men were a constant complication .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Baker</ENAMEX> had lots of them .
But she did n't trust them and did n't reward trust .
Her appetite for children also was large .
She made money , but spent more .
Friends pitched in .
Finally , Prince <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Rainier</ENAMEX> and Princess <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Grace</ENAMEX> saved her with the offer of a house in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Monaco</ENAMEX> .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Baker</ENAMEX> had the good luck to arrive in <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">1925</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Paris</ENAMEX> , where blacks had become exotic .
<ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">African</ENAMEX> art was in vogue and some intellectuals were writing breathlessly of a dawning age to be inspired by blacks .
To be exotic was to be patronized as well as prized , but for the most part <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Paris</ENAMEX> was a friendly island in a racist world .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Baker</ENAMEX> had bitter experience of bigotry from her <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">St. Louis</ENAMEX> childhood and <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">her days</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">New York</ENAMEX> theater , where she was judged too dark for an all - black chorus line -LRB- performing of course for all - white audiences -RRB- .
<ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Paris</ENAMEX> loved her at first sight .
`` One can hardly overemphasize the importance of her rear end , '' Ms. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Rose</ENAMEX> writes .
Ms. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Rose</ENAMEX> , who teaches literature at <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Wesleyan University</ENAMEX> , quickly proceeds to overemphasize , claiming that <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Baker</ENAMEX> 's dancing `` had uncovered a new region for desire '' and thereby ignoring <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">centuries</ENAMEX> of tributes to the callipygous .
`` <ENAMEX TYPE="WORK_OF_ART">Jazz Cleopatra</ENAMEX> '' contains other , more important , false notes that undermine what is , for the most part , a lively account of a life already familiar from earlier works .
To find parallels , other than sexual appeal , with <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Cleopatra</ENAMEX> , requires an equal stretch .
In <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Humphrey Bogart 's</ENAMEX> nightclub , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Victor Laszlo</ENAMEX> leads Free French sympathizers in `` <ENAMEX TYPE="WORK_OF_ART">La Marseillaise</ENAMEX> '' to drown out the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Nazis</ENAMEX> .
Ms. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Rose</ENAMEX> is best on <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">the early years</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="EVENT">World War II</ENAMEX> .
In her introduction , Ms. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Rose</ENAMEX> writes that she feels she has much in common with <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Baker</ENAMEX> , but as <ENAMEX TYPE="WORK_OF_ART">`` Jazz Cleopatra ''</ENAMEX> goes on , it seems more rushed , as though the author were growing less interested .
In <ENAMEX TYPE="WORK_OF_ART">`` Josephine Baker ''</ENAMEX> -LRB- <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Jonathan Cape</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">304</ENAMEX> pages , $ <ENAMEX TYPE="MONEY">35</ENAMEX> -RRB- , which was published in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Britain</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">last year</ENAMEX> and distributed in the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">U.S.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">this month</ENAMEX> , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Hammond</ENAMEX> has used his collection to produce an album of photographs and drawings of the star .
The text by <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Patrick O'Connor</ENAMEX> is a tough read , but the pictures make her magnetism clear and help explain why <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ernest Hemingway</ENAMEX> called <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Baker</ENAMEX> `` The most sensational woman anybody ever saw .
Or ever will . ''
Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Lescaze</ENAMEX> is foreign editor of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Journal</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
