<DOC DOCNO="bn/cnn/01/cnn_0144@0144@cnn@bn@en@on">
The talks will follow <ENAMEX TYPE="TIME">three hours</ENAMEX> of negotiations that went on <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">yesterday</ENAMEX> , against the backdrop of a <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Palestinian</ENAMEX> funeral for a <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">22 - year - old</ENAMEX> victim of the ongoing violence .
A senior adviser says <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Palestinian Authority</ENAMEX> President <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Yasser Arafat</ENAMEX> is working with President <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Clinton</ENAMEX> in a push for a peace agreement before Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Clinton</ENAMEX> leaves office .
</DOC>
