<DOC DOCNO="bn/cnn/01/cnn_0136@0136@cnn@bn@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Israel</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Labor Party</ENAMEX> has named <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ehud Barak</ENAMEX> its candidate for Prime Minister .
<ENAMEX TYPE="TIME">Hours</ENAMEX> before the announcement , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Barak</ENAMEX> tendered his resignation from the post , a move that forces a special election within <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">60 days</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
