<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!DOCTYPE inventory SYSTEM "inventory.dtd">

<inventory lemma="jihAz-n">
    
    <commentary> Plural أجهزة ; revised 6.28.08; revised 10.08.08
        
    </commentary>
    
    <sense n="1" type="" name="Equipment; anything kept for a specific useful purpose   كل شيء يحفظ وله مهمة خاصة وهو آلة " group="1">
        
        <commentary></commentary>
        
        <examples>
            
            هناك نقص في الأجهزة الطبية في بعض المستشفيات العراقية
            
            There is a shortage of medical equipment in some Iraqi hospitals.
            
            تحتوي الجامعات الأمريكية على أجهزة مخبرية يستخدمها الطلبة للتعلّم
            
            American universities have modern laboratory equipment that students use to learn.
            
            في العشرينات من القرن الماضي حدثت ثورة في أعداد وانواع الاجهزة المنزلية
            
            During the 1920s the types and amount of equipment used at home increased.
            
        </examples>
        
        <mappings>
            
            <wn version="0"></wn>
            
            <omega></omega>
            
            <pb></pb>
            
        </mappings>
        
        <SENSE_META clarity="" />
        
    </sense>
    
    <sense n="2" type="" name="Department; a group of people that have the same purpose   مجموعة من الأشخاص يوكل اليهم مهمة واحدة" group="1">
        
        <commentary></commentary>
        
        <examples>
            
            بعد إتفاقيات أوسلو تخلص بعض الفلسطينيين من الاحتكاك المباشر مع الأحتلال الاسرائيلي وعاشوا مراقبين من قبل 12 جهاز أمني فلسطيني -الجزيرة نت
            
            After the Oslo agreements some of the Palestinians got rid of the daily Israeli occupation forces only to find themselves ruled by 12 different Palestinian authority security departments. - aljazeera.net
            
            أحد أسباب الجهل  في الشرق الاوسط ان الحكومات الدكتاتورية تنفق على بناء أجهزة الأمن التي تحمي هذه الانظمة أكثر من إنفاقها على أجهزة التعليم والصحة
            
            One reason for ignorance and illiteracy in the Middle East is that the governments there spend more on the security departments that protect the regime than what they spend on educational and health care departments.
            
            إذا كنت مواطن في دولة عربية فانت تتعلم ان تخاف من غضب الله وجهاز المخابرات
            
            If you are a civilian in an Arab country you will learn to fear God and the intelligence department only.
            
        </examples>
        
        <mappings>
            
            <wn version="0"></wn>
            
            <omega></omega>
            
            <pb></pb>
            
        </mappings>
        
        <SENSE_META clarity="" />
        
    </sense>
    
    <sense n="3" type="" name="Bodily system; a set of organs or structures in the body that have a common function, like the nervous system مجموعة الاعضاء في الجسم لها وظيفة مينة مثل الجهاز العصبي" group="1">
        
        <commentary></commentary>
        
        <examples>
            
            جهاز المناعة هو الخلايا والانسجة المتنوعة في الجسم التى تمكنه من حماية نفسه ضد اي عدوى
            
            The immune system is the various cells and tissues in the body which make it able to protect itself against infection.
            
        </examples>
        
        <mappings>
            
            <wn version="0"></wn>
            
            <omega></omega>
            
            <pb></pb>
            
        </mappings>
        
        <SENSE_META clarity="" />
        
    </sense>
    
<sense group="1" n="4" name="none of the above" type="">
  <commentary>
Automatically generated NOTA sense (bbn)
  </commentary>
  <examples>
  </examples>
  <mappings>
    <wn version="2.1"></wn>
    <omega></omega><pb></pb>
    <fn></fn>
  </mappings><SENSE_META clarity=""/>
</sense>
    <WORD_META authors="Rashed Abu-Alia, Jaklin Salama, Gisele Ibrahim, Bonnie Stalls" sample_score="" />
    
    

<ita count="0" ann_1_2_agreement="0.0" />
</inventory>

