<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!DOCTYPE inventory SYSTEM "inventory.dtd">

<inventory lemma="Talab-n">
    
    <commentary>Sense added 08.08.08
        
    </commentary>
    
    <sense n="1" type="" name="Request" group="1">
        
        <commentary></commentary>
        
        <examples>
            
            طلب الرئيس الأمريكي من الرئيس المصري بأتباع الديموقراطية مع ان الرئيس الأمريكي لم تعجبه الديموقراطية ذاتها حين طبقها الفلسطينيين
            
            The American President requested that the President of Egypt adhere to democratic standards in Egypt elections, Although the American president disliked the out come these very standards yielded in Palestine
            
            طلب الرئيس الأمريكي من السعودية زيادة إنتاج النفط لكي تتراجع أسعار النفط
            
            The American president requested that Saudi Arabia increase its oil production so the oil prices would decrease
            
            قدم الموظف طلب لنقله إلى فرع آخر للشركة
            
            The employee put in a request to be transferred to another branch of the company.
            
            لقد رفض رئيسي في العمل طلبي بأخذ إجازة لمدة أسبوع
            
            My boss refused my request to have a vacation for a week.
            
        </examples>
        
        <mappings>
            
            <wn version="0"></wn>
            
            <omega></omega>
            
            <pb></pb>
            
        </mappings>
        
        <SENSE_META clarity="" />
        
    </sense>
    
    <sense n="2" type="" name="Application" group="1">
        
        <commentary></commentary>
        
        <examples>
            
            تقدمت بالعديد من الطلبات للعديد من الجامعات لدراسة الماجستير
            
            I submitted a number of applications to universities to do my Masters degree.
            
            يتقدم الكثيرون بطلب اللجوء الى الولايات المتحدة
            
            Many submit an application for asylum in the United States.
            
        </examples>
        
        <mappings>
            
            <wn version="0"></wn>
            
            <omega></omega>
            
            <pb></pb>
            
        </mappings>
        
        <SENSE_META clarity="" />
        
    </sense>
    
    <sense n="3" type="" name="Demand" group="1">
        
        <commentary></commentary>
        
        <examples>
            
            إن أسعار السوق للسلة والخدمات يتم تحديدها بناء على علا قة الطلب بالعرض
            
            The market prices of commodites and services are determined by the relationship of supply and demand.
            
            إن العرض والطلب هو نموذج اقتصادي يستخدم في نظرية المستهلك
            
            Supply and demand is an economic model used in consumer theory.
            
        </examples>
        
        <mappings>
            
            <wn version="0"></wn>
            
            <omega></omega>
            
            <pb></pb>
            
        </mappings>
        
        <SENSE_META clarity="" />
        
    </sense>
    
<sense group="1" n="4" name="none of the above" type="">
  <commentary>
Automatically generated NOTA sense (bbn)
  </commentary>
  <examples>
  </examples>
  <mappings>
    <wn version="2.1"></wn>
    <omega></omega><pb></pb>
    <fn></fn>
  </mappings><SENSE_META clarity=""/>
</sense>
    <WORD_META authors="Rashed Abu-Alia, Jaklin Salama, Bonnie Stalls" sample_score="" />
    
    

<ita count="0" ann_1_2_agreement="0.0" />
</inventory>

